Roman Towers妈妈会说，这只会永远恨我
Roman Towers mum do if she says this is just going to hate me forever
Jason Adam Baker
让我们更多地坚持布朗尼蛋糕
Let's stick with brownies more than advertised
我的祖母是从零开始的苹果馅饼桃子皮匠真正的王者
My grandmother was a real Baker Street from scratch apple pies peach cobbler
灰姑娘
Cinderella
哇
Wa
苹果梨片
Apple pear slices
我敢肯定有一种工具会很好
I'm sure there is a tool that would be good
看起来像
This looks like
Lidl duvet
拧你的苹果
Screw you Apple
就像苹果馅饼
It's like in apple pie
做个馅饼
Make a pasty
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do with this
好吧，如果你有一个苹果，你又走了一步，你已经扭曲了，说ABC
Alright so step one you again if you've got an apple you've got a twisted and say that ABC
是否借给您是您一生中都会遇到的人
Whether you lend is the person that you're going to end up with for the rest of your life
那是
That was
这个苹果
This Apple
着色一半
Colouring half
可以看到一些不错的香料
Can see some nice spices
试图取出种子
Tried to take out the seeds
我父亲做苹果馅饼
My father make apple pie
这是Mesa柴油机真正的最佳切片歌手
It's the best slice Mesa diesel real singer
如果我们要把苹果切成薄饼，不希望去皮，这是精心制作的方法，这将是我要做的第一件事
Is elaborate ways to slice an apple if we're getting it for a pie we don't want to remove the skin so that's going to be the first thing that I'm going to do
我的苹果没有皮，最简单的方式移除核心是将苹果切成
What's my Apple skinless the easiest way to remove the core is to cut the Apple into
4个一样
4 pieces which is the same
就在电线的侧面
Just at the side of the cord here
我刚好在corgi的身边
I have just to the side of the corgi
淡化我的苹果，然后
Play my Apple down and then
另外两个楔子
Two more wedges
软木塞弥补了，我可能会把所有这些切成约1/2英寸
Cork gone for making up I am probably going to slice all of these approximately 1/2 in
这样的东西
6 something like that
而这里的东西只是通过
And something here just come out through
然后我就拥有了美好的一面，并且自然而然地在生活中变得重要
And then I have nice even slices and natural important in life
那就是我所要知道的，只是将它放在小管道中
That's pretty much what I would do you know just put it inside little piping
苹果馅饼
Apple pie